A Guide to the Papers of Emily Couric, ca. 1983-2002
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Legislative Issues and Files
  - Health- Colorectal Cancer Screening Coverage (SB 1285 and SB 26), 2000 April-November (Box-folder 23:1)
  - Health- Colorectal Cancer Screening Coverage (SB 1285 and SB 26), 2001, n.d. (Box-folder 23:2)
  - Health- Emergency Contraceptives, 1997-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 23:3)
  - Health- Family Access to Medical Insurance Plan (FAMIS), 2000-2002 (Box-folder 23:4)
  - Health- Family Access to Medical Insurance Plans (FAMIS)- Report Exhibits, 2000 (Box-folder 23:5)
  - Health- HMO Denials (SB 955), 1999-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 23:6)
  - Health- Human Immunodeficiency Virus, 1996-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 23:7)
  - Health- Human Immunodeficiency Virus- Joint Subcommittee Studying the Issues, Policies, and Programs Relating with HIV- December 2, 1998 (HJR 269), 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 23:8)
  - Health- Informed Consent to Medical Procedure and Treatment, 1997-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Health- Insurance for Children Project, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Health- Insurance for Children Project- Free and Low-Cost Health Insurance: Children You Know are Missing Out, n.d. (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO), 1998-1999 January (Box-folder 24:4)
  - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO), 1999 February (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO), n.d. (Box-folder 24:6)
  - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO)- External Review Programs, 1998 (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO)- External Review Programs, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO)- Liability, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO)- Liability, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO)- Liability (SB 386), ca. 1997-1998 (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Health- Malpractice Cap, 1996-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Health- Managed Care, 1996-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 25:6)
  - Health- Martha Jefferson Hospital, 1995-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 25:7)
  - Health- Medical Assistants (SB 849), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 25:8)
  - Health- Mental Health, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 25:9)
  - Health- Mental Health, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 25:10)
  - Health- Midwives, 1987, 1990-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Health- Narrow Therapeutic Index Drugs, 1994, 1996-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 26:2)
  - Health- Nurse Practitioners, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 26:3)
  - Health- Nursing Homes and Long Term Care, 1985, 1987, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 26:4)
  - Health- Nursing Homes and Long Term Care, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Health- Nursing Homes and Long Term Care- Jefferson Park Center Closing, 2000 (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Health- Nursing Homes Voluntary Closure, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 26:7)
  - Health- Nursing Homes Voluntary Closure, 2001, n.d. (Box-folder 26:8)
  - Health- Out-of-Wedlock Births, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 27:1)
  - Health- Parental Notification (SB 1148), 1997 (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Health- Partial Birth Abortion, 1973, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Health- Partial Birth Abortion, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 27:4)
  - Health- Partial Birth Abortion, n.d. (Box-folder 27:5)
  - Health- Pharmacies- Joint Subcommittee Studying the Demise of Independent Pharmacies (HJR 158), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 27:6)
  - Health- Pharmacies- Joint Subcommittee Studying the Demise of Independent Pharmacies (HJR 158), 1996 January-August (Box-folder 27:7)
  - Health- Pharmacies- Joint Subcommittee Studying the Demise of Independent Pharmacies (HJR 158), 1996 September-December (Box-folder 27:8)
  - Health- Pharmacies- Joint Subcommittee Studying the Demise of Independent Pharmacies (HJR 158), 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 28:1)
  - Health- Pharmacies- Joint Subcommittee Studying the Demise of Independent Pharmacies (HJR 158)- January 8, 1997, 1996 (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Health- Pharmacies- Joint Subcommittee Studying the Demise of Independent Pharmacies (HJR 158)- January 8, 1997, 1997, n.d. (Box-folder 28:3)
  - Health- Pharmacists, 1996-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 28:4)
  - Health- Piedmont Geriatric Hospital, Burkeville, Virginia, 1998 (Box-folder 28:5)
  - Health- Prescription Drug Benefits (SB 1028), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 28:6)
  - Health- Prescription Drugs Consumer Advisor Panel, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 28:7)
  - Health- Prescription Drugs for Seniors, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 28:8)
  - Health- Prescription Drugs- HMO Waiting Periods for Drug Coverage, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 28:9)
  - Health- Prescription Drugs- Rating Panel (SB 723), 2000 (Box-folder 28:10)
  - Health- Qual Choice/ Sentara, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 28:11)
  - Health- Qual Choice/ Sentara, 1998 (Box-folder 28:12)
  - Health- Qual Choice/ Sentara, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 29:1)
  - Health- Region Ten Salary Classification and Compensation, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 29:2)
  - Health- Reproductive Rights, 1996-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 29:3)
  - Health- Sexually Transmitted Diseases- A Policymaker's Guide and Summary of State Laws, n.d. (Box-folder 29:4)
  - Health- Substance Abuse Treatment Providers Licensure Bill, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 29:5)
  - Health- Teen Pregnancy, 1999 (Box-folder 29:6)
  - Health- Tuberculosis Isolation Legislation, 1998 (Box-folder 29:7)
  - Health- Virginia Ambulatory Surgery Center, 1999 (Box-folder 29:8)
  - Health- Women's Health Initiative, 1993-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 29:9)
  - Helmet Law, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 29:10)
  - Historic Preservation, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 29:11)
  - Hobby and Model Boilers, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 29:12)
  - Housing, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Hugh Finn Case, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Hugh Finn Case, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Jackson River Litigation Over Property Rights, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 30:4)
  - James Madison Museum, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 30:5)
  - JAUNT, 2001 (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Jefferson Area Board for Aging (JABA), 1996-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 30:7)
  - Jefferson Area Board for Aging (JABA)- Collaborative Multi-Agency/ Jurisdictional Proposal to the Perry Foundation, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 30:8)
  - Judiciary- Magistrate, Jurisdiction of, 1998 (Box-folder 30:9)
  - Judiciary- Magistrate System Review, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 30:10)
  - Judiciary- Non Unanimous Juries, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 30:11)
  - Judiciary- Public Defender, 1994-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 30:12)
  - Judiciary- Public Defender Commission, 2001 (Box-folder 30:13)
  - Judiciary- Public Defender Staff- Budget Amendment, 1997-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 30:14)
  - Legal Aid Services, 1997-2002, n.d. (Box-folder 30:15)
  - Litton Marine Systems, 1999 (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Living Wage Campaign, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Madison County, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Madison County, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Madison County, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Madison County Office on Youth, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 31:6)
  - Madison Emergency Services (SB 953), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 31:7)
  - Madison Heritage Foundation- Kemper Residence- Budget Amendment, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 31:8)
  - Mattaponi Tribe, 1999 (Box-folder 31:9)
  - Metropolitan Washington Ear, Inc.- Toll-free Service Budget Amendment, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 31:10)
  - Miller School of Albemarle (SB285), 1986-1999 (Box-folder 31:11)
  - Montpelier Foundation, 1995-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 31:12)
  - Nelson County, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 31:13)
  - Nelson County, 1999-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Nelson County Community Center, n.d. (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Nelson County- Department of Social Services, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 32:3)
  - Nelson County Jail, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 32:4)
  - Nelson County Jail Budget Amendment, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Nelson County Route 29/ Food Lion Intersection, 2000 (Box-folder 32:6)
  - Nelson County- Route 56, 2000 (Box-folder 32:7)
  - Nelson County Rural Health Outreach Program, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 32:8)
  - Nelson County Rural Health Outreach Program- Budget Amendment, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 32:9)
  - Nelson County Senior and Community Center- Budget Amendment, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 32:10)
  - Nelson County - Transportation 2000 (Box-folder 32:10a)
  - Nelson County- Walton's Mountain Museum, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 32:11)
  - Old Dominion Electric Company- Gordonsville Power Plant, 1998, 2000 (Box-folder 32:12)
  - Open Burning Laws (SB 1029), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 32:13)
  - Open Burning Ordinances (SB 498), 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 32:14)
  - Orange County, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 32:15)
  - Orange County, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 32:16)
  - Orange County, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 33:1)
  - Orange County Courthouse Restoration, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 33:2)
  - Orange County Economic Development, 1996-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 33:3)
  - Orange County- Montpelier, 1999 (Box-folder 33:4)
  - Orange County School Board, 1995-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 33:5)
  - Orange County- Visitors' Center Tasting License, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 33:6)
  - Orange County Water Impoundment, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 33:7)
  - Orange County Youth Commission, 1995-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 33:8)
  - Paramount Theater- Charlottesville, VA, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 33:9)
  - Parent's Rights Constitutional Amendment (SJR 98), 1995-1996; 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 33:10)
  - Personal Responsibility and Work Opportunity Reconciliation Act of 1996, 1996 (Box-folder 33:11)
  - Piedmont Environmental Council, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 33:12)
  - Piedmont House, Charlottesville, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 33:13)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, 1996,1998, n.d. (Box-folder 33:14)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College- LPN Program, 2000 (Box-folder 33:15)
  - Pine Knot, Albemarle- Theodore Roosevelt Retreat, 1996, 2001, n.d. (Box-folder 34:1)
  - Police Issues, 1990-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Police- Law Enforcement Assistance Funding (HB599), 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 34:3)
  - Polling Place Identification, 1997 (Box-folder 34:4)
  - Property Owners Associations (SB 721), 2000 (Box-folder 34:5)
  - Preservation of Historic Property, Loans for (SB 959), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 34:6)
  - Public Hearings, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 34:7)
  - Rapidan Habitat for Humanity, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 34:8)
  - Rappahannock River Basin Commission, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 34:9)
  - Rappahannock River Basin Commission, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 34:10)
  - Recording for the Blind and Dyslexic, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 34:11)
  - Regional Industrial Facility Authorities, Creation of (SB 957), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 34:12)
  - Registrars- Employment Benefits, 1983, 1994-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 34:13)
  - Religious Right Movement, 1994-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 34:14)
  - Regional Competitiveness Act, 1997-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 34:15)
  - Rescue Squads, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 34:16)
  - Scottsville, Virginia, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 35:1)
  - Scottsville Town Charter (SB 37), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 35:2)
  - Scottsville- Quality of Life Committee, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 35:3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources- Aid to Families with Dependent Children, 1995 (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources- Temporary Assistance to Needy Families Advisory Committee TANF, 1996- May 1997 (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources- Temporary Assistance to Needy Families Advisory Committee TANF, June 1997- October 1997 (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources- Temporary Assistance to Needy Families Advisory Committee TANF, n.d. (Box-folder 35:7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources  Temporary Assistance to Needy Families Advisory Committee TANF, 1997 April 18, Notebook. (Box-folder 35:8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources- Temporary Assistance to Needy Families Advisory Committee TANF, 1997 November 10, Report. (Box-folder 35:9)
  - Senate Joint Memorial Resolution for Art Greene (SJ 478), 2001 (Box-folder 35:10)
  - Senate Joint Memorial Resolution for Carroll Shackelford (SJ 479), 2001 (Box-folder 35:11)
  - Senate Joint Memorial Resolution for John Paul Jay Monahan II (SJR 221), 1998 (Box-folder 35:12)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Commending Dave Mathews Band (SJ 346), 1996-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 35:13)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Commending Donald McCaig, Philip D. Moran, and Lou V. Crabtree (SJ 88), 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Commending George Welch (SJ 342), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 36:2)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Commending Jacob Foster/ Woodberry Forest, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 36:3)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Commending Joseph C. Palumbo, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 36:4)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Commending Dr. Robert F. Selden, JR (SJ 70), 2000 (Box-folder 36:5)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Commending Virginia Authors (SJ 494), 2001 (Box-folder 36:6)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Commending Virginia Wine Industry (SJ 321), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 36:7)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Concerning Disaster Assistance for Farmers (SJ 236), 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 36:8)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Concerning Internet Voting Study (SJ 189), 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 36:9)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Concerning Malcom Cole, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 36:10)
  - Senate Joint Resolution Concerning Meriwether Lewis McGinnis, 1999 (Box-folder 36:11)
  - Senate Joint Resolute Concerning Teacher Salaries, 1999 (Box-folder 36:12)
  - Senate Joint Resolution- Requesting the Secretary of Technology to conduct a study that results in a coordinated research and development policy for the Commonwealth (SJ 502), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 36:13)
  - Senior Citizens, 1995-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 36:14)
  - Senior Statesmen of Virginia, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 36:15)
  - Sheriffs, 1995-1998 August (Box-folder 36:16)
  - Sheriffs, 1998 September-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 36:17)
  - Smart Growth v. Urban Sprawl, 1998 (Box-folder 37:1)
  - Smart Growth v. Urban Sprawl, 1999 January-March (Box-folder 37:2)
  - Smart Growth v. Urban Sprawl, 1999 April-December (Box-folder 37:3)
  - Smart Growth v. Urban Sprawl, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 37:4)
  - Special Project, 1998 -2000 (Box-folder 37:5)
  - State Employees, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 37:6)
  - State Employees, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 38:1)
  - State Employees Grievance Procedure, 2000 (Box-folder 38:2)
  - State Employees- Gubernatorial Appointees Severance Packages (CSB 848), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 38:3)
  - State Employees- Gubernatorial Appointee Linda Byrd-Harden Severance Package, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 38:4)
  - State Employees- Health Insurance for Part-Time Employees (SB 728), 2000 (Box-folder 38:5)
  - State Employees- Lag Pay, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 38:6)
  - State Employees- MediChoice Budget Amendment, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 38:7)
  - State Employees- Reform of the Classified Compensation Plan, 1998-2000 June (Box-folder 38:8)
  - State Employees- Reform of the Classified Compensation Plan, 2000 July-August (Box-folder 39:1)
  - State Employees- Reform of the Classified Compensation Plan, 2000 September-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 39:2)
  - State Employees- Salary Increase 1996, 1996 March-October (Box-folder 39:3)
  - State Employees- Salary Increase 1996, 1996 November-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 39:4)
  - State Employees- Virginia Governmental Employees Association, 1997-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 39:5)
  - State Employees- Virginia Sickness and Disability Program, 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 39:6)
  - Stewards of Upper Rapidan, 2001 (Box-folder 39:7)
  - Taxes, 1992-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 39:8)
  - Taxes- Admissions Tax for Events, 1998 (Box-folder 39:9)
  - Taxes- Business, Professional and Occupational License (BPOL), 1996-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 39:10)
  - Taxes- Land Use, 1994-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 40:1)
  - Taxes- Meals Tax, 1996-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 40:2)
  - Taxes- Personal Property Tax Relief (Car Tax), 1997- January 1998 (Box-folder 40:3)
  - Taxes- Personal Property Tax Relief (Car Tax), February 1998-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 40:4)
  - Taxes- Refund for the Virginia Foundation for the Humanities (VFH), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 40:5)
  - Taxes- Retirement Income, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 40:6)
  - Taxes- Tax Credit For Adoption Expenses (SB 427), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 40:7)
  - Taxes- Tax Credit for Trust Income (SB 497), 1995-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 40:8)
  - Taxes-Tax Relief Indexing, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 40:9)
  - Technology Conversion, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 40:10)
  - Technology- State Surplus Computers for Charities (SB 285), 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 40:11)
  - Technology Transfer Resolution (SJR 502), 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 40:12)
  - Technology- Uniform Computer Information Transactions Act, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 40:13)
  - Technology- Virginia Assistive Technology Device Warranties Act (SB 402), 1998 (Box-folder 40:14)
  - Technology- Y2K Preparedness, 1999 (Box-folder 41:1)
  - Technopolis Team, 1999 (Box-folder 41:2)
  - Telecommunications Towers, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 41:3)
  - Telecommunications Towers, 1999 (Box-folder 41:4)
  - Telecommunications Towers, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 41:5)
  - Telecommunications- Public Rights-of-Way Use Fee, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 41:6)
  - Telecommunications- Tower Location Subject to Local Zoning, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 41:7)
  - Tobacco, 1991-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 41:8)
  - Tobacco Settlement, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 41:9)
  - Transportation, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 41:10)
  - Transportation- Billboards and Outdoor Advertising, 1992-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 42:1)
  - Transportation- Flattop Mountain, Greene County Problems, 1996 (Box-folder 42:2)
  - Transportation- Meadow Creek Parkway, 1995, 2000 (Box-folder 42:3)
  - Transportation- Photo Red Traffic Light (SB 846, etc), 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 42:4)
  - Transportation- Route 20 Accidents near Scottsville, 2000 (Box-folder 42:5)
  - Transportation- Route 29 Bypass, 1989-2000 (Box-folder 42:6)
  - Transportation- Secondary Roads, 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 42:7)
  - Transportation- Tourists Oriented Directional Signs (TODS), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 42:8)
  - Transportation- Western Transportation Corridor, 1998 (Box-folder 42:9)
  - Trash Importation- Memorializing Congress Resolution, 1999 (Box-folder 42:10)
  - United Way, 1995-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 42:11)
  - University of Virginia, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 42:12)
  - University of Virginia, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 42:13)
  - University of Virginia, 1999-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 43:1)
  - University of Virginia- Board of Visitors, 1999 (Box-folder 43:2)
  - University of Virginia- Labor Action Group on Living Wage, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 43:3)
  - University of Virginia Medical Center, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 43:4)
  - University of Virginia Medical Center- Codified Autonomy, 1996 (Box-folder 43:5)
  - University of Virginia Medical Center- Interest Income (SB 1384), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 43:6)
  - University of Virginia- Nuclear Reactor, 1997 (Box-folder 43:7)
  - University of Virginia- Qatar Satellite Campus, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 43:8)
  - Veteran's Day (Including Couric's Speech), 1995-1999 (Box-folder 43:9)
  - Virginia Center for the Creative Arts, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 43:10)
  - Virginia Center for the Creative Arts Budget Amendment, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 43:11)
  - Virginia Central Railroad, 1996 (Box-folder 43:12)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 1999 (Box-folder 43:13)
  - Virginia Festival of the Book, 1995-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 43:14)
  - Virginia Gateway for Technology Commercialization and Economic Development, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 43:15)
  - Virginia Horse Industry Board (SB 286), 1997 (Box-folder 44:1)
  - Virginia Industries for the Blind, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 44:2)
  - Virginia Lottery, 1996-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 44:3)
  - Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission, 2000 (Box-folder 44:4)
  - Volunteer Rescue Squads- Four- for- Life Bill, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 44:5)
  - Voting Machines, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 44:6)
  - Waste Management, 1999 (Box-folder 44:7)
  - Welfare Reform, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 44:8)
  - Wine Auction Banquet Licenses, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 44:9)
  - Wintergreen Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Resort License, 1998 (Box-folder 44:10)
  - Wolf Hybrids (HB 929), 1995-1997 (Box-folder 44:11)
  - Workers Compensation Commission, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 44:12)
  - WVPT- TV (PBS), 1999 (Box-folder 44:13)
  - WVPT- TV's Charlottesville Translator Move, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 44:14)
  - Youth Violence Project, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 44:15)
  - Legislative Session, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 45:1)
  - Legislative Session, [1998] (Box-folder 45:2)
  - Legislative Session- End of Session, 1998 (Box-folder 45:3)
  - Legislative Session- Veto Session, 1998 (Box-folder 45:4)
  - Legislative Session- Veto Session, 1998 (Box-folder 45:5)
  - Legislative Session, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 45:6)
  - Legislative Session- Evaluation, 1999 (Box-folder 45:7)
  - Legislative Session- News clippings, 1999 January (Box-folder 45:8)
  - Legislative Session- Veto Session, 1999 (Box-folder 45:9)
  - Legislative Session, 2000 (Box-folder 45:10)
  - Legislative Session- Budget Amendments, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 45:11)
- Series II: Campaign Materials
  - Subseries A: 1995 Campaign
    - Administrative- Financial Statements Amended, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 46:1)
    - Administrative- Financial Statements Amended, 1995 (Box-folder 46:2)
    - Administrative- Internal Revenue Service, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 46:3)
    - Administrative- Schedules, 1995 (Box-folder 46:4)
    - Administrative- Taxes, 1995 (Box-folder 46:5)
    - Administrative- Zip Codes, n.d. (Box-folder 46:6)
    - Campaign Calendar, 1995 (Box-folder 46:7)
    - Environmental Issues Group Meeting, 1995 June (Box-folder 46:8)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Campaign Money List, 1995 August 5 (Box-folder 46:9)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Charlottesville-Albemarle Business Fundraiser, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 46:10)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Convention Speech and Documentation, 1995 May 16 (Box-folder 46:11)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Debates, 1995 (Box-folder 46:12)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Family Fun Day Barbecue, 1995 (Box-folder 46:13)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Family Fundraiser, 1995 (Box-folder 46:14)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Fundraising Strategy, 1995 (Box-folder 46:15)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Grisham-Lorenzoni Event, 1995 (Box-folder 46:16)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Homecomings, 1995 (Box-folder 47:1)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Keswick, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 47:2)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Kids for Couric Fun Run, 1995 (Box-folder 47:3)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Lawyers for Couric, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 47:4)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Northern Virginia Fundraiser, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 47:5)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Nurses for Couric, 1995 (Box-folder 47:6)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Orange County/Madison County, 1995 (Box-folder 47:7)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Page (Nick and Irene), 1995 (Box-folder 47:8)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Richmond Fundraiser, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 47:9)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Smith College Function (7 Sisters Alumnae), 1995 (Box-folder 47:10)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Teachers for Couric, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 47:11)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Venable Women for Couric, 1994 (Box-folder 47:12)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Wintergreen, 1995 (Box-folder 47:13)
    - Land Use Issue Group, 1995 June 26 (Box-folder 47:14)
    - Media- Designs (Invites, Fliers, etc.), 1995 (Box-folder 47:15)
    - Media- Football Ads, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 47:16)
    - Media- Letters to the Editor, 1995 (Box-folder 47:17)
    - Media- Media Directions- Rich Savage, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 48:1)
    - Media - People Magazine, 1995 October 30 (Box-folder 48:2)
    - Media- Photo Release Forms, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 48:3)